[♪♪♪]
♪ I can't stop ♪
♪ The way I feel ♪
♪ Things you do ♪
♪ Don't seem real ♪
♪ Tell me what
you've got in mind ♪
♪ 'Cause we're running
out of time ♪
♪ Won't you ever set me free? ♪
♪ This waiting 'round's
killing me ♪
♪ She drives me crazy ♪
♪ Like no one else ♪
♪ And I can't help myself ♪
♪ I can't get ♪
♪ Any rest ♪
♪ People say ♪
♪ I'm obsessed ♪
♪ Everything you say is lies ♪
♪ But to me,
there's no surprise ♪
♪ What I had for you was true ♪
♪ Things go wrong,
they always do ♪
♪ She drives me crazy ♪
♪ Like no one else ♪
♪ And I can't help myself ♪
♪ I won't make it ♪
♪ On my own ♪
♪ No one likes ♪
♪ To be alone ♪
♪ She drives me crazy ♪
♪ Like no one else ♪
♪ And I can't help myself ♪
♪ She drives me crazy ♪
♪ Like no one else ♪
♪ And I can't help myself ♪
♪ She drives me crazy ♪
♪ Like no one else ♪
♪ And I can't help myself ♪
[♪♪♪]